Finding aid for the Aldous and Laura Huxley papers, 1925-2007 LSC.2009
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Aldous Huxley Papers
  - Photographs
    - Aldous Huxley portrait in wiriting studio profile at desk leaning on arms tweed blazer Llano CA, 1944; Photo ID No. 146; original photo signed Rose Nys Wessberg (Box 66, Folder 48)
    - Aldous Huxley portrait in writing studio hand to chin looking down tweed blazer Llano CA, 1944; Photo ID No. 146; original photo signed Rose Nys Wessberg (Box 66, Folder 48)
    - Aldous Huxley portrait in writing studio at desk looking down with pen tweed blazer Llano CA, 1944; Photo ID No. 146; original photo signed Rose Nys Wessberg (Box 66, Folder 48)
    - Aldous Huxley seated profile pointing with thumb, no date; Photo ID No. 147 (Box 66, Folder 49)
    - Aldous Huxley seated legs crossed looking off to side hands clasped, no date; Photo ID No. 148 (Box 66, Folder 50)
    - Aldous Huxley close up looking down light tie, no date; Photo ID No. 149 (Box 66, Folder 51)
    - Aldous Huxley close up black background, no date; Photo ID No. 150 (Box 66, Folder 52)
    - Aldous Huxley seated looking down black background, no date; Photo ID No. 150 (Box 66, Folder 52)
    - Aldous Huxley seated talking gesturing with hands, no date; Photo ID No. 151 (Box 66, Folder 53)
    - Program for Aldous Huxley lecture at MIT, 26-Sep-60; Photo ID No. 152; not photo (Box 66, Folder 54)
    - Aldous Huxley standing profile in hills above Hollywood, May-53; Photo ID No. 153 (Box 66, Folder 55)
    - Aldous Huxley standing in hills above Hollywood, May-53; Photo ID No. 153 (Box 66, Folder 55)
    - Pen and ink drawing (copy) of Aldous Huxley by David Levine from New York Review of Books, 1971; Photo ID No. 154; not photo (Box 66, Folder 56)
    - Aldous Huxley seated legs crossed, no date; Photo ID No. 155; not photo image from pamphlet? (Box 66, Folder 57)
    - Univeristy audience applauding Aldous Huxley, no date; Photo ID No. 155; not photo image from pamphlet? (Box 66, Folder 57)
    - Aldous Huxley with two unidentified men standing on hill above Bethlehem PA, no date; Photo ID No. 155; not photo image from pamphlet? (Box 66, Folder 57)
    - Aldous Huxley feet and shoes, 1937; Photo ID No. 155; not photo image from pamphlet? (Box 66, Folder 57)
    - Aldous Huxley, standing up looking down on Hollywood Hills, 1956 (Box 66, Folder 58)
    - Aldous Huxley as a younger man leaning forward, no date (Box 66, Folder 59)
    - Aldous and Laura Huxley, at home in Hollywood Hills, includes photos of Aldous and Laura reclining on bed and on chaise lounge outside, 1959; original Photo by Rosenys [Rose Nys?] (Box 66, Folder 60)
    - Aldous Huxley 3/4 talking black background (1), no date; Photo ID No. 156; mounted on cardboard (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Aldous Huxley 3/4 talking black background (2), no date; Photo ID No. 157; mounted on cardboard (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Aldous Huxley 3/4 talking black background (3), no date; Photo ID No. 158; mounted on cardboard (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Aldous Huxley 3/4 close up talking black background, no date; Photo ID No. 159; mounted on cardboard (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Aldous Huxley seated taking black background, no date; Photo ID No. 160; mounted on cardboard (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Aldous Huxley seated talking looking down black background, no date; Photo ID No. 161; mounted on cardboard (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Aldous Huxley seated talking looking down gesturing black background, no date; Photo ID No. 162; mounted on cardboard (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Aldous Huxley close up black background (2), no date; Photo ID No. 163; mounted on cardboard (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Aldous Huxley close up profile black background, no date; Photo ID No. 164; mounted on cardboard (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Aldous Huxley seated talking to unidentified man gesturing black background, no date; Photo ID No. 165; mounted on cardboard (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Aldous Huxley seated in chair talking gesturing with hands black background, no date; Photo ID No. 166; mounted on cardboard (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Aldous Huxley seated in chair looking down hands clasped black background, no date; Photo ID No. 167; mounted on cardboard (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Aldous Huxley profile looking down dark picture, no date; Photo ID No. 168; original photo by Phoenix Hamilton (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Aldous Huxley profile seated hands clasped around knees, no date; Photo ID No. 169 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Aldous Huxley and unidentified man holding two cartoons, no date; Photo ID No. 170 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Aldous Huxley seated in chair talking gesturing with hands black background (2), no date; Photo ID No. 171; mounted on cardboard (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Aldous Huxley close up 3/4 looking straight ahead black background, no date; Photo ID No. 172; mounted on cardboard (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Aldous Huxley portrait close up shadow on face, no date; Photo ID No. 173; original photo by Sanford H. Roth (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Aldous Huxley and unidentified man holding two cartoons and unidentified woman, no date; Photo ID No. 174 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Aldous Huxley close up looking down white handkerchief, no date; Photo ID No. 175 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Aldous and Laura Huxley at large gathering posed photograph, no date; Photo ID No. 176 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Laura Huxley portrait hand on neck, no date; Photo ID No. 177; original photograph by Jill Krementz (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Laura Huxley portrait hand to forehead, no date; Photo ID No. 178; original photograph by Jill Krementz (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Thomas Henry Huxley, 1857; Photo ID No. 179; photo attached to paper (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Aldous Huxley hand, 16-Nov-63; Photo ID No. 180 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Aldous Huxley on a train in Switzerland photo taken by Laura Huxley, 1961; Photo ID No. 181 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Aldous Huxley at podium at MIT, 1960; Photo ID No. 182 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Detail of Bernini's Ecstasy of St. Theresa, no date; Photo ID No. 183 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Postcard from Aldous Huxley to Laura Huxley of Bernini's head of Medusa, 1963; Photo ID No. 184 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Images used in This Timeless Moment, including Adromeda Galaxy, image of postcard, image of edited manuscript, image of The Polish Rider by Rembrandt, image of Aldous Huxley walking on grass, no date; Photo ID No. 185; Lick Observatory photograph (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Painted portrait of Aldous Huxley by Biberman, no date; Photo ID No. 186 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Drawn portrait of Aldous Huxley by B. Budwig, no date; Photo ID No. 187 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Clipping of article titled Remembering Aldous Huxley by Huston Smith from Los Angeles Times, 20-Nov-88; Photo ID No. 188; illustrated with photograph of Aldous Huxley (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Clipping of article titled If My Library Burned Tonight by Aldous Huxley (2), 1947; Photo ID No. 189; Clipped article from House and Garden, illustrated with photograph of Aldous Huxley by George Platt Lynes. (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Clipping of article titled If My Library Burned Tonight by Aldous Huxley (1), 1947; Photo ID No. 189; Clipped article from House and Garden, illustrated with photograph of Aldous Huxley by George Platt Lynes (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Clipping of article titled A Case for ESP PK and PSI by Aldous Huxley from Life Magazine (1), 11-Jan-54; Photo ID No. 190; illustrated with photograph of Aldous Huxley, and experiments in ESP (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Clipping of article titled A Case for ESP PK and PSI by Aldous Huxley from Life Magazine (7), 11-Jan-54; Photo ID No. 190; illustrated with photograph of Aldous Huxley, and experiments in ESP (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Clipping of article titled A Case for ESP PK and PSI by Aldous Huxley from Life Magazine (2), 11-Jan-54; Photo ID No. 190; illustrated with photograph of Aldous Huxley, and experiments in ESP (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Clipping of article titled A Case for ESP PK and PSI by Aldous Huxley from Life Magazine (5), 11-Jan-54; Photo ID No. 190; illustrated with photograph of Aldous Huxley, and experiments in ESP (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Clipping of article titled A Case for ESP PK and PSI by Aldous Huxley from Life Magazine (6), 11-Jan-54; Photo ID No. 190; illustrated with photograph of Aldous Huxley, and experiments in ESP (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Clipping of article titled A Case for ESP PK and PSI by Aldous Huxley from Life Magazine (4), 11-Jan-54; Photo ID No. 190; illustrated with photograph of Aldous Huxley, and experiments in ESP (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Clipping of article titled A Case for ESP PK and PSI by Aldous Huxley from Life Magazine (3), 11-Jan-54; Photo ID No. 190; illustrated with photograph of Aldous Huxley, and experiments in ESP (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Clipping of article titled Aldous Huxley's life and times in southern california by Lisa Mitchell from The Los Angeles Times, no date; Photo ID No. 191; illustrated with photograph of Aldous Huxley (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Clipping of article from Italian language newspaper by Alfredo Todisco, no date; Photo ID No. 192; illustrated with photograph of Aldous Huxley (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Aldous Huxley walking outside with unidentified woman, no date; Photo ID No. 193; magazine article, Harpers Bazaar, illustrated with photograph of Aldous Huxley and unidentified woman (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Clipping of article titled A Warm Climate for Cultural Life, no date; Photo ID No. 194; illustrated with photograph of Aldous and Julian Huxley, Christopher Isherwood, Gerald Heard, and Linus Pauling (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Clipping of article titled We nominate for the Hall of Fame from Vanity Fair, no date; Photo ID No. 195 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Aldous Huxley seated outside looking down next to citrus tree, 1961; Photo ID No. 196 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Aldous Huxley close up leaning on elbow hand to cheek looking down, 1958; Photo ID No. 196; original photograph by W. Suschitzky U.K. (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Aldous Huxley profile leaning on arm smiling, no date; Photo ID No. 196; original photo by Sanford H. Roth (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Aldous Huxley seated profile hand to mouth at café, no date; Photo ID No. 196 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Aldous Huxley close up checked tie (2), 1958; Photo ID No. 197; original photograph by W. Suschitzky U.K. (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Aldous Huxley close up checked tie (1), 1958; Photo ID No. 197; original photograph by W. Suschitzky U.K. (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - D.H. Lawrence, no date; Photo ID No. 198; original photography by Sanford H. Roth (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Igor Stravinsky, no date; Photo ID No. 198; original photography by Sanford H. Roth (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Aldous Huxley with Edith Sitwell in Hollywood, 1950s; Photo ID No. 199 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Aldous Huxley with two unidentified people at exhibit, 1961; Photo ID No. 199 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Aldous and Julian Huxley seated (3), 1958; Photo ID No. 200; original photograph by W. Suschitzky U.K. (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Aldous and Julian Huxley seated (2), 1958; Photo ID No. 200; original photograph by W. Suschitzky U.K. (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Aldous and Julian Huxley seated (1), 1958; Photo ID No. 200; original photograph by W. Suschitzky U.K. (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Aldous Huxley with Ginny Laura Paula and Juan Pfeiffer, no date; Photo ID No. 201 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Aldous Huxley seated outside next to Laura Huxley and her father, no date; Photo ID No. 202 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Aldous Huxley seated with arms around Paula [Kathy?] and Juan Pfeiffer, no date; Photo ID No. 202 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Aldous Huxley standing next to young Piero Archera [?], no date; Photo ID No. 202 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Aldous Huxley with Laura Huxley with other unidentified women, no date; Photo ID No. 202 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Aldous Huxley looking at camera smiling seated next to Laura Huxley, no date; Photo ID No. 202 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Aldous Huxley with newspaper seated with Laura Huxley looking over his shoulder, no date; Photo ID No. 202 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Aldous Huxley at dinner party with Jinny Pfeiffer and unidentified people, no date; Photo ID No. 202 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Aldous Huxley seated to right near Laura Huxley and her family [?], no date; Photo ID No. 202 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Slides, The Dartmouth Convocation on Great Issues of Conscience in Modern Medicine, 1960 Sep 8-10; Photo ID No. 255 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Slides, painting of Aldous Huxley by Edward Biberman, no date; Photo ID No. 255 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Negative strip, Aldous Huxley and Julian Huxley, no date; Photo ID No. 255 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Negative strips, Aldous Huxley, and unidentified others [Copenhagen, with Dr. Wolf?], 1961 [?]; Photo ID No. 255 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Small negatives, individually labeled, miscellaneous, 1960s; Photo ID No. 256 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Large negatives, individually labeled, miscellaneous, no date; Photo ID No. 257 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Photos of Aldous Huxley's funeral in Surrey, England, [1964] (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Photo of Andrew Huxley and family, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Photo of Marguerite Nys, includes correspondence, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Psychedelics
    - Hoffman, Albert
      - Correspondence, 1961 - 1963 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Leary, Timothy
      - LSD, Materials Related to Harvard Experiments, 1960 - 1962 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1962 - 1964 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Various Manuscripts Sent to Aldous Huxley, 1962 Oct 26; The Religious Experience: Its Production and Interpretation; Religious Implications of Consciousness Expanding Substance; Tibetan Manual For Ego-Transcendent Experience Using Psychedelic Substances; A Change Program for Adult Offenders Using Psilocybin; including newsletters and meeting minutes; includes letter from Leary to Aldous Huxley (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence to Aldous Huxley from Metzner and Osmond, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Materials Related to the International Federation for Internal Freedom, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - LSD
      - On The Responsible Use of LSD-25 In Psychiatric Treatment: A Preliminary Report, 1963 Feb 7 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - LSD Session Notes in Laura Huxley's handwriting, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Notes on LSD and Mescaline, typewritten, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - LSD and Religion, Transcription of discussion at a Huxley luncheon in Toronto, 31 Mar 1961 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous articles on the use and experimentation of psychedelics in medicine and psychiatry, 1960s; Contains materials collected by Laura Huxley post Aldous Huxley's death (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Transcript of discussion "On Conciousness Altering Drugs" given at California College of Medicine, 18 Apr 1956; Featuring Aldous Huxley and Gerlad Heard, Moderator is Oscar Janiger (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Osmond, Humphrey
      - Correspondence, 1961-1967; Regarding house fire, psychedelics and psychology (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Recordings
      - Label reads: Double Tape (LSD Flower) [illegible] on the litter tape [?] recorder & cancel it; Laura Huxley, notes on LSD session [that was dedicated to Aldous' LSD session the day he died], notes on Aldous' LSD session the day he died, 14 Dec 1963; UCLA Tape No. 403; related to UCLA Tape No 378 A and 378 B
      - Aldous Huxley and Laura Huxley, recorded conversation [while on psilocybin?]; Label reads: A & L Bylocyclin [spi?], 8 pills (2 mg.), 3-3/4" ips, 1962 Jan 22; UCLA Tape No. 13; Note on box: "A & L talking." Note on cassette: "Love and work." (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - Aldous Huxley, recorded by Laura Huxley, label on box reads "A. LSD 100 mg", 1962 Dec 23; UCLA Tape No. 210; Note on box:" A. LSD 100 mg. 23 Dec 62." (Box 98, Folder 16)
      - Laura Huxley, interview, LSD, 1975 Sep; UCLA Tape No. 236; Typed label reads: "Laura -LSD Spet. '75" (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Research Related
      - Psilocybin, Experiment Results, Aldous Huxley Participant, Photocopy, 1960 Nov 6 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Retrospectives
    - Recordings
      - Laura Huxley, George Dewey Cukor, Christopher Isherwood and Robert Maynard Hutchins, Program on Aldous Huxley, USC, 1965 Mar 18; UCLA Tape No. 146; 3-3/4 ips, tracks 1 & 2. Friends of the Libraries, USC. (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - Retrospective, "Ideas", "Aldous Huxley and Beyond: Heredity and the Man", Part I, Hosted by Barry Morse, Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, 1973 Dec 3; UCLA Tape No. 149; Note on reel label: 3.75. Note on box: "Heredity and the man. Copyright held by C.B.C. Not to be played commercially without approval." "A. Huxley ideas" (label on reel) (Box 94, Folder 12)
      - Retrospective, "Ideas", "Aldous Huxley and Beyond: Vision", Part II, Hosted by Barry Morse, Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, 1973 Dec 4; UCLA Tape No. 150; Note on reel label: 3.75. Note on box: "Vision. Copyright held by C.B.C. Not to be played commercially without approval." "Ideas A. Huxley" (label on reel) (Box 94, Folder 13)
      - Retrospective, "Ideas", "Aldous Huxley and Beyond: Brave New World", Part III, Hosted by Barry Morse, Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, 1973 Dec; UCLA Tape No. 151; Note on reel label: 3.75. Note on box: "Ideas: Aldous Huxley and beyond. Programme #3. Brave New World. Dub at 3/3/4 ips (119-to 116). Copyright held by C.B.C. Not to be played commercially without approval." (Box 94, Folder 14)
      - Retrospective, "Ideas", "Aldous Huxley and Beyond: Mystic Vision", Part IV, Hosted by Barry Morse, Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, 1973 Dec; UCLA Tape No. 152; Note on box: "Ideas: Aldous Huxley and beyond. Programme #3. Mystic vision. Dub at 3/3/4 ips (119-to 117). Copyright held by C.B.C. Not to be played commercially without approval." (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Retrospective, "Ideas", "Aldous Huxley and Beyond: Beyond", Part V, Hosted by Barry Morse, Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, 1973 Dec 7; UCLA Tape No. 153; Note on reel label: 3.75. Note on box: "Huxley # 5 'Beyond'. Copyright held by C.B.C. Not to be played commercially without approval." (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Retrospective, Aldous Huxley, speaker, Yehudi Menuhin: Friends and Contemporaries, BBC Archives, WFMT Chicago Fine Arts Station; Aldous Huxley reading aloud, Brave New World, 1966; UCLA Tape No. 198; 3-3/4, monoraul. Note on box: "Side 1 MS tape #H-13 (A. Huxley): Dupe of Yehudi Menuhin: Friends and contemporaries, from BBC archives, Side 2: MS tape #H-10, A. Huxley reading section "Linda's Death" from his novel, Brave New World, from Columbia record ML-4753." Note on tape label: "Side 1 mono, 3-3/4, 5/15/66, SFMT, Chicago." (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Retrospective, Aldous Huxley, no date; UCLA Tape No. 222; Five cassette tapes (Box 99)
      - Laura Huxley, Tribute to Aldous Huxley, Brave New world and Virtual Reality, New York Open Center Symposium, Manhattan., 1994; UCLA Tape No. 221; Two cassette tapes (Box 99)
      - Tribute to Aldous Huxley, Laura Huxley and other presenters, Brave New world and Virtual Reality, New York Open Center Symposium, Manhattan (continued from UCLA Tape no. 221 A), 1994; UCLA Tape No. 221B; See 221 (Box 99, Folder 11)
      - Tribute to Aldous Huxley, Laura Huxley and other presenters, Brave New world and Virtual Reality, New York Open Center Symposium, Manhattan., 1994; UCLA Tape No. 221A; See 221 (Box 99, Folder 11)
      - Tribute to Aldous Huxley, Laura Huxley and other presenters, Brave New world and Virtual Reality, New York Open Center Symposium, Manhattan (continued from UCLA Tape no. 221 B), 1994; UCLA Tape No. 221C; See 221 (Box 99, Folder 12)
      - Retrospective, Aldous Huxley, no date; UCLA Tape No. 222A; See 222 (Box 99, Folder 13)
      - Retrospective, Aldous Huxley (continued from UCLA Tape no. 222 A), no date; UCLA Tape No. 222B; See 222 (Box 99, Folder 14)
      - Retrospective, Aldous Huxley (continued from UCLA Tape no. 222 B), no date; UCLA Tape No. 222C; See 222 (Box 99, Folder 15)
      - Retrospective, Aldous Huxley (continued from UCLA Tape no. 222 C), no date; UCLA Tape No. 222D; See 222 (Box 99, Folder 16)
      - Retrospective, Aldous Huxley (continued from UCLA Tape no. 222 D), no date; UCLA Tape No. 222E; See 222 (Box 99, Folder 17)
      - Retrospective, Aldous Huxley: Perceptions and Prophesies, Ideas on Aldous Huxley, hosted by Lister Sinclair, no date; UCLA Tape No. 226; Four cassette tapes, Handwritten label reads: "Aldous Memorial from Toronto." REBURN - CD HAS SCRATCH AND NOISY IN CD PLAYER. (Box 100)
      - Retrospective, Aldous Huxley: Perceptions and Prophesies, Ideas on Aldous Huxley, hosted by Lister Sinclair, no date; UCLA Tape No. 226A (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Retrospective, Aldous Huxley: Perceptions and Prophesies, Ideas on Aldous Huxley, hosted by Lister Sinclair (continued from UCLA Tape no. 226 A), no date; UCLA Tape No. 226B (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Retrospective, Aldous Huxley: Perceptions and Prophesies, Ideas on Aldous Huxley, hosted by Lister Sinclair (continued from UCLA Tape no. 226 B), no date; UCLA Tape No. 226C (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Retrospective, Aldous Huxley: Perceptions and Prophesies, Ideas on Aldous Huxley, hosted by Lister Sinclair (continued from UCLA Tape no. 226 C), no date; UCLA Tape No. 226D (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Safe Contents
    - Correspondence and outline of film by Ginny Pfeiffer, Rome, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Typed draft, The Desert by Aldous Huxley, no date (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Clipping of text with typed annotations, no date (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Typed draft, Faith, Taste, and History by Aldous Huxley, includes correspondence from Chatto & Windus, no date (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Typed draft with annotations, Education on the Nonverbal Level by Aldous Huxley; Typed draft, Matter, Mind, and the Question of Survival by Aldous Huxley, no date; 1960 May 10 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Photos, notes, and sketches by Aldous Huxley, no date (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Photographic copies of drawbridge sketch by Aldous Huxley, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Typed draft of Aldous Huxley's account of Maria Huxley's death, [1955?] (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Typed draft, letter from Laura Huxley to Julian and Juliette Huxley regarding Aldous Huxley's death, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, reply to Laura Huxley's letter regarding Aldous Huxley's death from Julian and Juliette Huxley, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Photocopy, holograph note by Aldous Huxley requesting LSD on deathbead, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Holograph and typed drafts of correspondence from Laura Huxley to Aldous Huxley, 1961-1963 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence and notes from Aldous Huxley to Laura Huxley regarding edits of Recipes for Living and Loving, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Audio DVDs and transcription of discussion between Laura Huxley and Aldous Huxley regarding Shakespeare and Religion, 1963[?] (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Two volumes [possibly volumes mentioned by psychic in reference to Aldous Huxley's communication from afterlife], no date (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, from Aldous Huxley to Laura Huxley, includes original drawbridge sketch and love letters [1 of 2], 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, from Aldous Huxley to Laura Huxley, includes original drawbridge sketch and love letters [2 of 2], 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Photos of Aldous Huxley, miscellaneous, includes original photo of Aldous Huxley by Lou Stoumen, no date (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Typescript of pages from Island by Aldous Huxley, 1963[?] (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Photocopy, letter from Aldous Huxley to Gabriel Pascal, 1951 Dec 16 (Box 79, Folder 7)